Guide to the Creative Time Archive 1973-2006 MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Grants, Development, and Financial Correspondence, 108324
  - Subseries A: NEA Grants, 108409
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, Presenting Organizations, #12-5440-070, 1981-1982; 108502 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - NEA - Museum Program, #12-4442-737 [Art on the Beach], 1981-1982; 108501 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #12-4129-236 [Art on the Beach, Masstransiscope, Ruckus Manhattan], 1981-1982; 108500 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, Services to the Field [documentation, Resource Center], 1981-1982; 108499 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - NEA - Dance Program, #22-3341-090 [Art on the Beach], 1982-1983; 108498 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - NEA - Advancement Grant, 1983; 108497 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - NEA - Dance Program, #32-3341-00282 [Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage], 1983; 108496 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #32-4170-00470 [Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage], 1983-1985; 108495 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - NEA - Visual Artists Organization application, 1983-1984; 108494 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - NEA - Music Program, #42-4442-0057, #42-B147-0241 [Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage, Nighttrippers, etc.], 1983-1984; 108493 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - NEA - Music Program, #32-3124-00303 [Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage], 1983-1984; 108492 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - NEA - Museum Program, #42-4442-00057 [Art on the Beach], 1984; 108491 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - NEA - Museum Program, #42-4442-00058 [Art in the Anchorage], 1984; 108490 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, Art in Public Places, rejection [A Drop in the Bucket, Jane Greengold], 1984; 108489 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - NEA - Dance Program, #42-3341-0323 [Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage, Nighttrippers], 1984-1985; 108488 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042233638
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, #5442-0016 [publicity, documentation, promotional], 1984-1985; 108487 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - NEA - Museum Program, Special Exhibitions application [Art on the Beach], 1984-1985; 108486 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #42-4121-0045 [Art on the Beach, Masstransiscope, Art in the Anchorage, South Street Seaport], 1984-1985; 108485 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #42-4121-0045, receipts, etc. [Art on the Beach, Masstransiscope, Art in the Anchorage, South Street Seaport], 1984-1985; 108484 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, rejected [Stroll Magazine publication], 1985; 108483 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts/Rockefeller Foundation Re-Grant Program, 1985; 108482 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - NEA - Dance Program, #52-3341-0269 [Art in the Anchorage, Art on the Beach], 1985-1986; 108481 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #52-4121-0040 [Art on the Beach, A Drop in the Bucket, Masstransiscope, B.Holden to Diderot, Memory Theatre of Giulio Camillo], 1985-1986; 108480 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - NEA - Music Program, #52-3147-0058 [Art in the Anchorage, Art on the Beach], 1985-1986; 108479 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, #52-5442-0023 [development, PR, financial management, etc], 1985-1986; 108478 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - NEA - Worksheet, Status Reports, 1986; 108477 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #86-4121-0090 [Performance in the Park, Art in the Anchorage, Art on the Beach, Masstransiscope], 1986; 108476 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - NEA - Arts Advancement Program, #86-4724-0195 [Donation of Apple IIe computer], 1986; 108475 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, #86-5442-0072 [Art in the Anchorage], 1986; 108474 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - NEA - Music Program, #86-3147-0141 [Art in the Anchorage, Performance in the Park], 1986-1987; 108473 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - NEA - Dance Program, #86-3341-0308 [Art on the Beach], 1986-1987; 108472 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - NEA - Design Arts Program, #87-4170-0005 [Art on the Beach], 1987; 108471 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - NEA - Design Arts Program, #86-4231-0164 [Art on the Beach], 1987; 108470 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, #87-5442-0054 [Art in the Anchorage, Performance in the Park, Art on the Beach], 1987; 108469 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #87-4121-0098 [Art in the Anchorage], 1987-1988; 108468 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - NEA - Music Program, #87-3147-0127 [Art in the Anchorage, Art on the Beach, Performance in the Park, Wintergarden], 1987-1988; 108467 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - NEA - Dance Program, #87-3341-0242 [Art on the Beach], 1987-1988; 108466 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, #88-5442-0079 [Wintergarden, Art in the Anchorage, Art on the Beach, Survival Research Laboratories], 1988; 108465 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - NEA - Design Arts, rejection [Battery Maritime Building project], 1988; 108464 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #88-4141-0168 [Art in the Anchorage, Art on the Beach, UP Tiempo!, citywide], 1988; 108463 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - NEA - Dance Program, #88-3341-0199 [Art in the Anchorage, Art on the Beach, UP Tiempo!], 1988-1989; 108462 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - NEA - report material, financial documentation, 1988-1989; 108461 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - NEA - Music Program, #88-3147-0539 [Art in the Anchorage, Art on the Beach, UP Tiempo!], 1988-1989; 108460 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - NEA - Design Arts, #89-4251-0067 [Battery Maritime Building], 1989-1990; 108459 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042233646
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #89-4121-0075 [Art in the Anchorage, Citywide], 1989-1990; 108458 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - NEA - Dance Program, #89-3341-0326 [UP Tiempo!, Citywide], 1989-1990; 108457 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, #89-5442-0131 [Art in the Anchorage, Citywide], 1989-1990; 108456 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - NEA - Music Program, #89-3147-0109 [Art in the Anchorage, Creative Time at Dixon Place, etc.], 1989-1990; 108455 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, rejection [Honeymoon Project], 1989-1990; 108454 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - NEA - Music Program, #90-3147-0107 [Citywide, Art in the Anchorage], 1990-1991; 108453 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, rejection [Station House Opera], 1990-1991; 108452 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, #90-5442-0048 [Citywide, Station House Opera, Bowery Concert, Dixon Place, Honeymoon Project, Love of a Poet, SUZ/o/SUZ, Art in the Anchorage], 1990-1991; 108451 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #90-4121-0070 [Citywide, Black Sheep II, Station House Opera, Bowery Concert, Carbon Monoxide…, Electric Blanket, First in the Front Line…, Honeymoon Project, Love of a Poet…], 1990-1991; 108450 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - NEA - Dance Program, #90-3341-0326 [Station House Opera, Bowery Concert, SUZ/o/SUZ], 1990-1991; 108449 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, rejection [The Castle Mutes], 1991-1992; 108448 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - NEA - Music Program, #91-3147-0270 [Art in the Anchorage], 1991-1992; 108447 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #91-4121-0059 [Art in the Anchorage, First on the Front Line…, Memories of NY Chinatown, Masterpieces Without the Director, Billboard Project, Domestic Violence Milk Carton, Transitions Inc, Sacrificial Ornament], 1991-1992; 108446 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, #91-5442-0044 [Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors, As a Dream that Vanishes, Roy Cohn/Jack Smith, Public/Private], 1991-1992; 108445 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - NEA - Design Arts, #91-4251-0077 [Battery Maritime Building], 1991-1992; 108444 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #92-4121-0060 [Art in the Anchorage, Citywide], 1992-1993; 108443 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - NEA - Dance Program, #92-3341-0221 [Higher Ground, Ringside], 1992-1993; 108442 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, #92-5442-0002 [Citywide, Battery Maritime Building, Art in the Anchorage], 1992-1993; 108441 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - NEA - Music Program, #92-3147-0216 [Victory Music Series], 1992-1993; 108440 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #93-4121-0136 [42nd St Art Project, In Honor of Allen R. Schindler, Underdevelopment in Progress/500 Years, Billboard Project, Patina du Prey's Memorial Dress], 1993-1994; 108439 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - NEA - Presenting and Commissioning Program, Dance, rejection, 1993-1994; 108438 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - NEA - Dance Program, #93-3341-0220 [Elizabeth Streb/Ringside], 1993-1994; 108437 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - NEA - Presenting and Commissioning Program, Music, rejection, 1993-1994; 108436 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - NEA - Music Program, #93-3149-0055 [Art in the Anchorage, Citywide], 1993-1994; 108435 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - NEA - Presenting and Commissioning, #93-5443-0078, 1993-1994; 108434 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #94-4121-0025 [42nd St Art Project], 1994; 108433 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - NEA - Misc., 1994-1997; 108432 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - NEA - Presenting and Commissioning, #94-4121-0025 [42nd St Art Project, Combat Zone, Poster Campaign, Billboard Project, Building Sweeps], 1994-1995; 108431 (Box 9, Folder 98)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042233653
    - NEA - Music Program, rejection, 1995; 108430 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #95-4121-0080 [Art in the Anchorage, Time Capsule, Rent-A-Body], 1995; 108429 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, Art in Public Places [Cyberwide], 1995; 108428 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - NEA - Presenting and Commissioning, #95-5443-0116 [Art in the Anchorage, Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors], 1995-1996; 108427 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #95-4143-0163 [Creative Time website, Cyberwide, Virtual Arts Residency], 1995-1996; 108426 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - NEA - Presenting, Music, #95-5447-0019 [Art in the Anchorage, Winter Music], 1995-1996; 108425 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - NEA - Cancellation of Visual Arts Program, 1996; 108424 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - NEA - Presenting, Dance, rejection, 1996; 108423 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #96-4121-0023 [Art in the Anchorage], 1996-1997; 108422 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - NEA - Presenting, rejection, 1996-1997; 108421 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - NEA - Advancement, Quarterly Reports, 1981-1985; 108420 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - NEA - Advancement, Grant and Requirements, 1983; 108419 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - NEA - Advancement, General, 1983-1987; 108418 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - NEA - Advancement, Apple Computer Grant, 1986-1987; 108417 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - NEA - Site Visits and Reports [Women's Graphic Center materials], 1981; 108416 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - NEA - Challenge Grant, 1980-1981; 108415 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - NEA - Grant for Handicapped Accessibility, 1980; 108414 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - NEA - Audit, 1985-1986; 108413 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - NEA - Misc. Final Reports, Financial Reports, 1982-1986; 108412 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - NEA - Grant Amounts, 1982-1987; 108411 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - NEA - Supporting Documentation, Undated; 108410 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Subseries B: NYSCA Grants, 108376
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Ruckus Manhattan, Sail, Crafts in Action, Plaza Event ] -see also following year Application folder, 1974-1975; 108408 (Box 10, Folder 120)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042233661
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Anemones, Neon Rainbow, Ruckus Manhattan, Round], 1975-1976; 108407 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - NYSCA - Budgets and Worksheets, 1975-1976; 108406 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - NYSCA - Report [Anemones, Neon Rainbow, Ruckus Manhattan, Round], 1975-1976; 108405 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - NYSCA - Architectural and Environmental Arts, Technical Assistance Grant, 1975-19777; 108404 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Administration, Environmental Painting, Kite and Wind Sculpture, Light Sculpture, Art Education], 1976-1977; 108403 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - NYSCA - Interim and Final Report, 1976-1977; 108402 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Butler's Lives of the Saints, Masstransiscope, Custom and Culture], 1977-1978; 108401 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - NYSCA - Contracts and Final Reports, 1977-1978; 108400 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Masstransiscope, Downtown Drive-in, Storefronts, Custom and Culture, Art on the Beach], 1978-1979; 108399 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - NYSCA - Contracts and Final Reports, 1978-1979; 108398 (Box 10, Folder 130)
    - NYSCA - Music Program Application and Supplementary Material [Custom and Culture], 1978; 108397 (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - NYSCA - Presenting Application and Supplementary Material [Custom and Culture], 1979; 108396 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Documentation and Resource Center, Masstransiscope, Downtown Drive-In, Art on the Beach], 1979-1980; 108395 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - NYSCA - Contracts, 1979-1980; 108394 (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Art on the Beach, Windspun], 1980-1981; 108393 (Box 10, Folder 135)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Art on the Beach, Ruckus Manhattan, Documentation Resource Center], 1981-1982; 108392 (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - NYSCA - Final Report, 1981-1982; 108391 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    - NYSCA - Work papers, 1982; 108390 (Box 10, Folder 138)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage], 1982-1983; 108389 (Box 10, Folder 139)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage], 1983-1984; 108388 (Box 10, Folder 140)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage, Nighttrippers], 1984-1985; 108387 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [B. Holden to Diderot, A Drop in the Bucket, Masstransiscope, Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage], 1985-1986; 108386 (Box 10, Folder 142)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Art in the Anchorage, Performance in the Park, Art on the Beach, Stroll Magazine], 1986-1987; 108385 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - NYSCA - Architecture Grant Application and Supplementary Material [Art on the Beach], 1986-1987; 108384 (Box 10, Folder 144)
    - NYSCA - Program Guidelines and Application Deadlines Publication, 1987-1988; 108383 (Box 11, Folder 145)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042233679
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Art in the Anchorage, Art on the Beach, Survival Research Laboratories, Wintergarden, Performance in the Park], !987-1988; 108382 (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - NYSCA - Final Report, 1987-1988; 108381 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Battery Maritime Building, Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage, UP Tiempo!, Wintergarden], 1988-1989; 108380 (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - NYSCA - Battery Maritime Building Plans/Materials, 1988-1989; 108379 (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Citywide, Art in the Anchorage, Black Works, Wilds and the Deep], 1989-1990; 108378 (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - NYSCA - Applications and Supplementary Material [Citywide, Art in the Anchorage, Love of a Poet, Bowery Concert, 1989-1990; 108377 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Subseries C: DCA Grants, 108360
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Custom and Culture], 1977-1978; 108375 (Box 12, Folder 152)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042233687
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Art on the Beach], 1978-1979; 108374 (Box 12, Folder 153)
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Art on the Beach], 1979-1980; 108373 (Box 12, Folder 154)
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Ruckus Manhattan], 1981-1982; 108372 (Box 12, Folder 155)
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Art on the Beach], 1984-1985; 108371 (Box 12, Folder 156)
    - DCA - City Correspondence, 1984; 108370 (Box 12, Folder 157)
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Masstransiscope], 1984; 108369 (Box 12, Folder 158)
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage], 1985-1986; 108368 (Box 12, Folder 159)
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Art in the Anchorage, Performance in the Park, Art on the Beach], 1986-1987; 108367 (Box 12, Folder 160)
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Performance in the Park, Art on the Beach, Art in the Anchorage, 1987-1988; 108366 (Box 12, Folder 161)
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Citywide, Art in the Anchorage, Art on the Beach, UP Tiempo!], 1988-1989; 108365 (Box 12, Folder 162)
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Citywide, Art in the Anchorage], 1989-1990; 108364 (Box 12, Folder 163)
    - DCA - Misc./Review of Projects [Art in the Anchorage, Citywide, etc.], 1989-1991; 108363 (Box 12, Folder 164)
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Art in the Anchorage, Citywide], 1990-1991; 108362 (Box 12, Folder 165)
    - DCA - Application and Supplementary Material [Art in the Anchorage, Citywide] continued from previous folder, 1990-1991; 108361 (Box 12, Folder 166)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous Grants, 108355
    - Meet the Composer - Application, 1977-1978; 108359 (Box 12, Folder 167)
    - Institute of Museum Studies - Application and Supplementary Materials, 1979-1981; 108358 (Box 12, Folder 168)
    - Meet the Composer - Application, 1980; 108357 (Box 12, Folder 169)
    - Institute of Museum Studies - Application and Supplementary Materials, 1985-1986; 108356 (Box 12, Folder 170)
  - Subseries E: Development, 108341
    - Development - Con Edison, 1981-1995; 108354 (Box 13, Folder 171)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042233695
    - Development - Chemical Bank, 1981-1995; 108353 (Box 13, Folder 172)
    - Development - Citibank, 1982-1995; 108352 (Box 13, Folder 173)
    - Development - Mary Cary Trust, 1984-1995; 108351 (Box 13, Folder 174)
    - Development - New York Community Trust, 1984-1991; 108350 (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - Development - Lannan Foundation, 1986-1989; 108349 (Box 13, Folder 176)
    - Development - Lef Foundation, 1987-1998; 108348 (Box 13, Folder 177)
    - Development - Lila Wallace, Reader's Digest Fund, 1987-1988; 108347 (Box 13, Folder 178)
    - Development - Pew Charitable Trust, 1988-1990; 108346 (Box 13, Folder 179)
    - Development - The Nathan Cummings Foundation, 1989-1995; 108345 (Box 13, Folder 180)
    - Development - Dance Theater Workshop, Suitcase Fund, 1991; 108344 (Box 13, Folder 181)
    - Development - Jules and Doris Stein Foundation; Art Matters, 1994-1996; 108343 (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - Development - Buhl Foundation, 1995; 108342 (Box 13, Folder 183)
  - Subseries F: Financial Correspondence, 108334
    - Correspondence - Harbor Festival, 1977-1988; 108340 (Box 13, Folder 184)
    - Correspondence - Robert Sterling Clark Foundation, Management Grant, 1979-1980; 108339 (Box 13, Folder 185)
    - Correspondence - Jerome Foundation [Windspun], 1980-1981; 108338 (Box 13, Folder 186)
    - Correspondence - Warner Communications, 1980; 108337 (Box 13, Folder 187)
    - Correspondence - Beard's Fund, Inc, 1980; 108336 (Box 13, Folder 188)
    - Correspondence - General, 1980; 108335 (Box 13, Folder 189)
  - Subseries G: Funding Miscellaneous, 108325
    - Deposit Forms, 1975-1976; 108333 (Box 13, Folder 190)
    - In-Kind Funding, 1979-1980; 108332 (Box 13, Folder 191)
    - Budget, 1979-1980; 108331 (Box 13, Folder 192)
    - Funding Requests, 1978-1979; 108330 (Box 13, Folder 193)
    - Funding Requests, 1979-1980; 108329 (Box 13, Folder 194)
    - Advancement, 1983-1987; 108328 (Box 13, Folder 195)
    - Advancement, 1983-1984; 108327 (Box 13, Folder 196)
    - Advancement, In-Kind, 1983-1984; 108326 (Box 13, Folder 197)
- Series III: Slides, 108144
  This series contains all slides from the Creative Time Archive. Slides have been arranged into binders by project chronologically by year, respective of the order as received from Creative Time. Each sleeve has been given a unique alphanumeric designation according to binder arrangement. Slide content primarily includes exhibition and performance documentation and the majority of slides were received with substantial annotation as to the project, artist, date, and photographer. Subdividers before each project provide names of most photographers and artists represented therein.
  - Crafts in Action - Galleria at 100 William Street, 1974; 108323 (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeves A1-A2)
  - Sail - 88 Pine Street, 1975; 108322 (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeves A3-A7)
  - Ruckus Manhattan - 88 Pine Street, 1975-1976; 108321 (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeves A8-A12)
  - Anemones - 88 Pine Street, 1976; 108320 (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeves A13-A17)
  - New York Sky Events: Neon Rainbow - 59th Street Pond, Central Park, 1976; 108319 (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeves A18-A19)
  - New York Sky Events: East Harlem Sky Events - East Harlem, 1976; 108318 (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeves B1-B2)
  - Custom and Culture - US Custom House, 1 Bowling Green, 1977; 108317 (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeves B3-B6)
  - Butler's Lives of the Saints - 88 Pine Street, 1977; 108316 (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeves B7-B9)
  - Art on the Beach 1 - Battery Park City Landfill, 1978; 108315 (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeves B10-B16)
  - Custom and Culture - US Custom House, 1 Bowling Green, 1979; 108314 (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeves B17-B19)
  - Masstransiscope - Myrtle Street Subway Station, 1980; 108313 (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeves C1-C2)
  - Art on the Beach 2 - Battery Park City Landfill, 1980; 108312 (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeves C3-C13)
  - Breaking in - First Precinct House, 48 Old Slip, 1980; 108311 (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeves C14-C18)
  - Art on the Beach 3 - Battery Park City Landfill, 1981; 108310 (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeves D1-D10)
  - Projects at the Precinct, 48 Old Slip, 1981; 108309 (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeves D11-D13)
  - Ruckus Manhattan Revival - Burlington House Lobby, 1345 6th Avenue, 1981-1982; 108308 (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeves E1-E4)
  - Art on the Beach 4 - Battery Park City Landfill, 1982; 108307 (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeves E5-E10)
  - Principles in Perspective - Chamber of Commerce, 65 Liberty Street, 1982; 108306 (Box Binder E, Folder Sleeves E11-E13)
  - Art on the Beach 5 - Battery Park City Landfill, 1983; 108305 (Box Binder F, Folder Sleeves F1-F6)
  - Art in the Anchorage 1 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1983; 108304 (Box Binder F, Folder Sleeves F7-F11)
  - Walk-in Theater For Pedestrians - US Courthouse, 40 Foley Square, 1983; 108303 (Box Binder G, Folder Sleeve G1)
  - Art on the Beach 6 - Battery Park City Landfill, 1984; 108302 (Box Binder G, Folder Sleeves G2-G9)
  - Touch Sanitation - Marine Transfer Station, 59th Street, 1984; 108301 (Box Binder G, Folder Sleeves G10-G11)
  - Art on the Beach 7 - Battery Park City Landfill [slide script from CT inserted before slides], 1985; 108300 (Box Binder H, Folder Sleeves H1-H16)
  - Art on the Beach 7 - Battery Park City Landfill (continued from previous binder), 1985; 108299 (Box Binder I, Folder Sleeves I1-I16)
  - Art in the Anchorage 2 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1985; 108298 (Box Binder J, Folder Sleeves J1-J14)
  - A Drop in the Bucket - Franklin Street, 1985; 108297 (Box Binder K, Folder Sleeves K1-K3)
  - Christie's Benefit By the Sea - Christie's, 1985; 108296 (Box Binder K, Folder Sleeves K4-K7)
  - Art in the Anchorage 3 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, 1986; 108295 (Box Binder L, Folder Sleeves L1-L7)
  - B. Holden to Diderot - US Courthouse, 40 Foley Square, 1986; 108294 (Box Binder L, Folder Sleeves L8-L12)
  - Performance in the Park - Central Park Bandshell, 1986; 108293 (Box Binder M, Folder Sleeves M1-M11)
  - Performance in the Park - Central Park Bandshell (continued from previous binder), 1986; 108292 (Box Binder N, Folder Sleeves N1-N10)